<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Posts on Reenchantment</title><link>https://reenchantment.band/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Reenchantment</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 20:09:16 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://reenchantment.band/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Comrade Victor Biography</title><link>https://reenchantment.band/posts/comrade-victor-biography/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 20:09:16 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://reenchantment.band/posts/comrade-victor-biography/</guid><description>Comrade Victor is a rock star, cult leader, revolutionary, mad genious and spiritual visionary that is descended from interplanetary royalty. He has arrived to earth to liberate the ignorant minds of humanity from the forces of evil and wickedness. You ignore him at your own peril. You must send him all of your money and give him total control over mind and body immediately.
Comrade Victor</description></item><item><title>About Reenchantment</title><link>https://reenchantment.band/posts/about-reenchantment/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 04:59:08 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://reenchantment.band/posts/about-reenchantment/</guid><description>Mystical Rock Music by Victor Fisher Reenchantment is a rock and metal solo project by Victor Fisher. The name originates from Max Weber&amp;rsquo;s theory of disenchantment. The goal of the project is to reenchant the world through the use of music or other spiritual practices. Please visit the links page for more information.
Victor Fisher photo</description></item><item><title>Reenchantment Reviews</title><link>https://reenchantment.band/posts/reenchantment-reviews/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 04:08:18 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://reenchantment.band/posts/reenchantment-reviews/</guid><description>1. Spirit Writing Album Review by D. Kelvin of Forgotten Songs Spirit Writing album blue
Here what the so-called Reverend of Despair (his real name is Victor Fisher and he&amp;rsquo;s from a band called Shroud of Delirium) wrote on Encyclopaedia Metallum to present this album: &amp;ldquo;I have been working on this new solo project due to the absence of my band. Although plagued by mediocre production (alternate: although blessed with obscure production) I thought this may interest some of you.</description></item><item><title>Reenchantment Links</title><link>https://reenchantment.band/posts/reenchantment-links/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 03:37:22 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://reenchantment.band/posts/reenchantment-links/</guid><description>✉️ Contact Form reenchantment.bandcamp.com
💰 Donate Paypal Link
🎧 Short Demo songs.reenchantment.band/short-demo
🎤 Recordings Archive songs.reenchantment.band
📽️ YouTube Channel youtube.com/@reenchantment
📁 Experimental Archive victorsarchive.com</description></item><item><title>Reenchantment Timeline</title><link>https://reenchantment.band/posts/reenchantment-timeline/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 02:00:37 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://reenchantment.band/posts/reenchantment-timeline/</guid><description>2006 Victor Fisher started playing guitar after discovering classic rock bands like The Beatles, Queen, Led Zeppelin, Deep Purple, Steppenwolf, Creedence Clearwater Revival, Rare Earth and Jefferson Airplane.
Victor had previously been a violin player in school orchestra with an interest in folk music, disco music and movie soundtracks.
2007 After getting into heavier bands such as Slayer, Metallica, Lamb of God, Melechesh, and Amon Amarth, Victor was inspired to discover what the heaviest possible music is.</description></item><item><title>The Legend of Reenchantment</title><link>https://reenchantment.band/posts/the-legend-of-reenchantment/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 00:27:09 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://reenchantment.band/posts/the-legend-of-reenchantment/</guid><description>Around the year two thousand and six, a troubled artist known as The Lord Reverend Wizard of Alchemical Despair discovered a collection of sacred relics on the very fringes of our reality. These priceless and terrifying artifacts provided an extraordinary glimpse into the mysteries of rock music and the dark arts.
The Reverend of Despair suffers from a rare form of psychosis
The Reverend of Despair immediately began assembling a team of experts known as Shroud of Delirium to help him disseminate this revolutionary information to the wider world.</description></item></channel></rss>